The world is awash in pain.
The Great War was the biggest war in human history,
and it left the world's nations with deep scars.
There's Corpse,
just like Teach predicted.
That's impossible...
There was over two hundred meters between us!
It's conclusion brought about
a radical change in world affairs.
Eat this, yo!
I've got more where that came from!
Urgh...
He moves with such poise.
But we've got a surprise for him up ahead!
That's the spot!
The politicians all realized how poor
the cost-performance of war was.
Due to how advanced modern science was,
weapons were too effective at killing.
Yeesh, that's one ugly mug you've got.
Well, well, looks like you have some chops.
Compliments from the enemy?
That's a new one.
For all your talent, though...
you're green as hell.
Bonfire! My rival!
We finally meet!
With that, the era of nations pointing their guns
at each other out in the open came to an end.
Now, battles are fought between spies
over information -
in shadow wars.
We managed to avoid having any civvies get hurt.
Magnificent.
You're not going to kill him?
This is something you need to remember.
When a spy gets captured,
the only fate that awaits them is a
darkness deeper than death.
So, we still don't have a lead on their whereabouts?
I hope they just forgot what day
they were supposed to come back.
Given who we're talking about,
I don't think that's likely.
We should assume that something,
or someone, must be stopping them.
MISSION: Forgetter I
We ran a background check on Uwe's new maids,
and it came back clean.
Got it.
Thanks for taking care of that.
That was some fine work, rooting out
and capturing Corpse's co-conspirator Olivia.
Uwe is a good man, so it means a lot that
they were able to keep him alive.
It would seem that Flower Garden, Pandemonium,
Meadow, and Daughter Dearest
are capable of operating just fine, even without you.
I don't know if I'd go that far.
Your chosen squad of Glint, Dreamspeaker,
Forgetter, and Fool
did an excellent job capturing Corpse, as well.
That's true.
They all showed striking levels of growth
on this last mission.
However, what's this I hear about the
chosen squad failing to return?
You're still keeping us under observation?
Draw whatever conclusions you like.
Here at HQ, we're considering the possibility
that they've turned traitor
and are planning on organizing a manhunt.
Don't.
Let me handle this one in-house.
There's no need for you to get involved.
Seriously, out with it already.
What have you all been spending
this past month doing?
That's right! I've been really curious.
And why'd my bedroom get blown up?
There was a mishap.
I'm sorry, what?
It was the day we set out on the Corpse mission.
Before Setting Out For the Corpse Mission
Good hunting out, you all.
Promise me you'll come back in one piece.
Of course, and thank you for seeing us off.
What's wrong, Lily?
There isn't much pep in your step.
It's nothing, I was just a bit worried.
I was afraid this whole selection process would
make things awkward between us.
Oh, I'm not mad in the slightest.
If anything, I'm happy that your hard work
is getting recognized.
Well, all right then!
Chosen Wunderkind Lily is on the job!
They're gone, right?
I'M SO MAAAAAAAD!
I was so sure I was going to get chosen!
What's wrong with me, huh?!
Why won't Teach respect my talents?!
Oh, be quiet.
Teach!
How much of that did you hear?
Pull yourself together.
I have an important job for you.
I sent Grete and the other three off to
root out one of Corpse's allies.
You four are the ones I'm taking with me
to actually fight Corpse.
That makes perfect sense.
I never doubted you for a moment, Teach.
Corpse won't hesitate to kill a dozen bystanders
if it will let him assassinate his target.
The objective is to capture him
without suffering a single civilian casualty.
Doing that will require manpower,
but I'm not interested in bringing
you along just to have you die.
That's why I've prepared a test for you.
What kind of test?
Touch my hand by the time evening falls.
That's the test.
If you fail, I'll have to fight Corpse on my own.
I'm confident that you're up to the challenge.
This is what I selected the
team's strongest members for.
Leave it to us.
We won't betray your trust!
Magnificent.
Come on, everyone, let's have a strategy meeting!
Wait, what?
There's one thing you should know.
Monika, Erna, and Annette all ran into
setbacks at their academies
due to their inability to cooperate with others.
However, completing this mission is going to
require rock-solid teamwork.
I get that, but you're not saying...
Bring the team together.
This is the important job you had for me?!
I thought I'd start with the most reasonable of the three
and work my way up, but I guess that's off the table.
All those times I actually led us were
when we had the whole team here.
Lily's antics always lightened the mood,
and that combined with Sybilla's retorts and
Sara's reactions were what really brought us together.
And Grete's the one person who can hold
a decent conversation, but now she's gone, too.
Still, I need to find a way for us to work together!
Did that come from Lily's room?
What, did you need something?
For starters, what are you doing in Lily's room?
There's something I wanted to look into
while we had the place nice and empty.
About Heat Haze Palace, you mean?
What do you want?
Isn't it obvious?
I want to talk.
How are we going to pass the test?
That hardly seems worth discussing.
It's not like teaming up with you lot is going to
be enough for me to complete it.
Well, don't just go deciding that on your own!
Can you leave now?
I'm going to fly this one solo.
Let's chat, Erna.
Wh- Erna!
We need to talk!
Erna, open up!
You keep your room really neat, don't you?
So, Erna, about that test-
Wow.
I fought through my shyness to let
someone into my room
and have a conversation with them.
I'm all tired out now, so I'm going to take a nap.
But we haven't even talked about anything yet!
Forget rock-solid, we aren't rock-anything.
Plus, this last girl is the one that
worries me most of all.
Amnesia?
That's right, Annette doesn't remember anything
from before she joined her academy.
Her papers list her as being fourteen,
but it's unclear if even that's true.
She got taken in by the state with
no memories or birth certificate.
So, that's why her code name is Forgetter...
Annette, I know you're in here.
Come on, Annette.
Up and at 'em.
I'm awake, yo!
What's up, Sis?
I'm at kind of a loss about this test Teach gave us.
Would you mind helping me out?
Oh, I already gave it a go.
Huh?
I was all like, "Bro, let me touch your hand,"
but he said no!
That's why I went to bed in a huff!
It can't be done!
There's no way I can corral those three!
I have to get these mice to
the handler by this afternoon.
I'm sorry, but I don't have time for this right now.
Between this and that tantrum earlier,
you really need to work on your mental fortitude.
You think I don't know that?
Now that I think about it,
you're oddly well-informed about Inferno.
Why is that?
I guess I am.
Seven years ago, a crimson-haired woman
from Inferno saved my life.
She's my savior, and the person I aspire to be like.
I see.
A crimson-haired woman?
That would be code name Hearth.
She was Inferno's previous boss.
We were as close as a family in Inferno,
but we fought constantly.
Our boss was a kind person,
but when we were arguing,
she could be as stubborn as the best of them.
We all had our own opinions,
and those opinions often came into conflict.
I have to say, I'm a bit surprised.
"Enjoy that discord."
"Differences between allies are
the key to a strong team."
That's a quote I cribbed off the boss.
Ms. Hearth said that?
That's right.
The best approach is to butt heads
with your teammates directly.
What has she been up to?
"Faucets: garden, kitchen,
main bath, all done. Bathroom..."
Is this information about Heat Haze Palace?
"Lily: slightly larger than other bedrooms."
"Old boss's room?"
Lily's room used to belong to Ms. Hearth?
If you hone that ability of yours,
you'll be the strongest spy around.
But the thing is,
I don't want you to be just any old spy.
I want you to become a hero.
I'm going to go protect the citizens
you once gave your all to defending.
And I'm going to do it with the power
you helped me discover.
I'm code name Dreamspeaker,
and it's time to lure them to their ruin.
MISSION: Forgetter I
I really should have continued that
conversation with Big Sis Thea.
Why, if it isn't Erna!
There's no need to look so startled.
Are you on cooking duty?
Who's your partner?
It's Big Sis Monika.
She left me a note that said to wait here
and went off somewhere.
What, she blew you off?
I, um...
About earlier...
Tell me, Erna, do you want to become close with me?
Be honest.
Would you want to get close with me,
even if it meant having to expose
your innermost secrets?
I... I do.
I want to.
Then, for the next three seconds,
would you mind looking me in the eye?
Erna...
You want a real big sister, don't you?
So, that's why you call us all "Big Sis."
Dearie me...
You want so badly to be doted on,
but you hold it back and never let it show.
That's not it.
I just don't want you to get
caught up in my misfortune...
What a big baby.
No! That's not true!
It's okay.
I'll be your big sister.
You can cry, and I won't tell the others.
Oh, my adorable little sister.
Yeep...
You don't have to be ashamed.
Just throw away your ideals and
be honest with yourself.
I can fulfill all the secret wishes
you can't share with anyone else.
What did you just do to Erna?
Just a little trick I know.
I can see what people desire.
I don't learn any details, though.
I'd be happy to teach you how to do it, too.
In fact, I can teach you all
my techniques for seducing men.
I literally couldn't be less interested.
Oh, no, it's really all right.
I'll have you know that I taught Grete
everything she knows about seduction!
So you're the one behind her pathetic
attempts at sexual harassment?
Hey now, she's doing her best!
I swear, you're all a bunch of softies.
Spies need to be ruthless,
and that's something this team is sorely lacking.
What are you doing?
Oh hey, it's Thea!
The faucet was broken, so I fixed it, yo!
Why are there three of them now?
I replicated everything,
from its shape down to its stains.
There's only one right one,
and if you turn the wrong one,
it makes a huge explosion!
You really are an genius when it comes to tinkering.
Say, Annette...
Do you want to get close with me?
Even if it means having to
open your heart up to me a bit?
Yup!
I wanna get close with you, Sis!
Okay, then can you look me in the eye?
My body's fighting back?
It's telling me not to look into Annette's heart?
How'd it go, Sis?
Did you see my desires?
Yes, well, um, is it just me...
or have you gotten taller lately?
That's amazing, Sis!
You can tell?
I totally did, yo!
I've grown three whole millimeters in the past month.
And it's all because I changed the way I sleep!
Well, once we finish the test,
I'll make you some milk pudding.
Yo, that'll make me grow even taller!
Annette's mind is like that of a five-year-old.
All I was able to find in there was
a desire to grow taller.
Is there really nothing else that she wants?
Milk pudding! Milk pudding!
All right, gang, let's go finish this test!
I'm in, yo!
Yeep!
What's wrong, Big Sis Thea?
It just feels like it was such a battle getting here...
It seems as though Lily's room used to
belong to Inferno's old boss.
I'm going to use that fact to lure Teach inside.
Annette, I need you to rig Lily's room with traps.
Roger that, yo!
Erna, your job is going to be to
narrowly slip past the traps
and touch Teach's hand.
You got it!
Now, let's do this!
It's time for us to show just what we're made of!
There we go, all done.
Did you not end up working together?
Touching your hand was as easy as
preventing you from washing it.
What's going on here?
Klaus was handling animals.
People always wash their hands after they do that.
I broke the faucet out in the garden ahead of time.
Then, I stationed Erna in the kitchen
and sent Annette over to the other bathroom.
The communal bath is girls-only,
so Teach was never gonna go there.
The only place left for him to wash his hands
was the sink in this bathroom here.
All I had to do was lie here in wait.
Remember what I told you?
I have to hand the pets over to
the handler this afternoon,
so I'm short on time.
My only option was to give up and offer her my hand.
Thanks, by the way.
You all made for a great diversion.
W-we what?
That note I left in Lily's room got you real fired up, huh?
I appreciate you babysitting the kids like that.
N-now listen here!
Magnificent.
"Differences between allies are
the key to a strong team."
What I expect out of you four
is for you to cooperate by butting heads
and stripping each other's egos raw.
By pushing each other, you push yourselves forward.
That's how we're going to defeat Corpse.
Hey, good for you.
You picked up my scraps,
and now you get to go on the mission.
I've had about enough of your snark.
Hey, Sis...
We've been waiting for Klaus to
show up for forever, yo.
Is he coming?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Monika actually already finished the test.
What a bummer!
And after I added a second doorknob
and made it so that if you turned the wrong one,
everything would explode, too!
You need to disarm it at once.
It's not like anyone would fall for anything
that obviously suspicious, but still...
How unlucky...
When I got back from the bathroom,
there was an extra doorknob.
I feel like this is Erna's fault for fiddling with stuff
when she knows how unlucky she is.
I say it's Annette's fault for using such
a ridiculous amount of blasting powder!
I was just following Thea's orders, yo.
A-as far as I'm concerned,
none of this would have happened
if Monika had just worked with us from the start!
You are not pinning this on me.
I guess I need to make one amendment.
I won't ask you to be the best of friends...
...but...
...please at least try to work together.
...and that's how it all went down.
Is it just me, or do those four sound kinda unhinged?
Be that as it may, they're each incredibly talented.
They completed the mission without a hitch.
Oh yeah, well, if they were really that great,
they wouldn't have blown up my room!
Afterwards, they decided to take
some time off at the mission site.
So, we still don't know why they haven't called.
We need to go look for them.
You all go on ahead.
I have another mission to take care of,
but I'll join up with you as soon as I can.
I disagree.
Every second could very well end up mattering.
You should prioritize the search efforts.
Yeah, go help out the others.
I know it's not much,
but I'll do what I can to help out here.
You've really grown to be dependable.
Understood.
I'll leave the mission to you.
But, um, what about me?
Lily, you're with me.
The two of us are going to go track down our team.
You got it!
This will be an emergency mission.
We need to find our missing teammates.
After the Corpse Mission -
Seriously, what's the deal with this place?
Four Days Before the Others Began Their Search
Why go to a pool at night?
And what's with the skeevy lighting?
We just finished a mission, didn't we?
Sometimes, you have to give yourself
a little reward to make it all worth it.
If Klaus hadn't given us specific orders,
I would have ditched you ages ago.
And if you did that,
who would have looked after the kids?
Behold, my special deluxe squirt gun!
Open fire, yo!
Yeep!
How unlucky...
You've probably noticed too,
but Annette's engineering is beyond
anything our nation is capable of.
It does seem that way.
Where'd she come from, I wonder?
Who are you?
I'm this girl's mother.